[
    {
        "id": 1,
        "question": "1 x 1",
        "choices": [10, 1, 5, 6],
        "correct": 1
    },
    {
        "id": 2,
        "question": "4 x 1",
        "choices": [2, 5, 3, 4],
        "correct": 4
    },
    {
        "id": 3,
        "question": "6 x 2",
        "choices": [6, 4, 12, 3],
        "correct": 12
    },
    {
        "id": 4,
        "question": "3 x 4",
        "choices": [7, 12, 14, 15],
        "correct": 12
    },
    {
        "id": 5,
        "question": "4 x 1",
        "choices": [9, 4, 1, 2],
        "correct": 4
    },
    {
        "id": 6,
        "question": "10 x 1",
        "choices": [10, 0, 20, 25],
        "correct": 10
    },
    {
        "id": 7,
        "question": "1 x 2",
        "choices": [2, 9, 11, 3],
        "correct": 2
    },
    {
        "id": 8,
        "question": "7 x 2",
        "choices": [8, 14, 9, 5],
        "correct": 14
    },
    {
        "id": 9,
        "question": "3 x 2",
        "choices": [7, 6, 14, 15],
        "correct": 6
    },
    {
        "id": 10,
        "question": "8 x 1",
        "choices": [8, 0, 16, 3],
        "correct": 6
    }
]